barneys.com 2019-06-25

# Barneys New York Site

## Introduction

Thank you for visiting Barneys New York. This Privacy Policy explains how Barneys New York, Inc. and our subsidiaries and affiliated companies (collectively, “Barneys New York,” “we” or “us”) collect, use, and disclose information through our website and applications (collectively, the “Services”), when you shop in our stores, when you engage with us on social media, or when you otherwise interact with us. 

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will communicate any such changes by updating the date at the top of the policy, and in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our websites’ homepages or sending you a notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you access the Services or otherwise interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the choices available to you. 

## Information Collection

_Information You Provide to Us_

We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you create an account, make a purchase, create a gift registry and wish list, make a reservation at our restaurants, make an appointment with a personal shopper, fill out a form or survey, participate in a contest or promotion, apply for a job, communicate with us via third party social media sites, request customer support, or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card or gift card information and any other information you choose to provide. If you create an account online, we may ask for additional information, such as your birthday, gender, and product preferences. 

_Information Automatically Collected_

When you access or use our Services, we automatically collect information about you, including:

  * _Log and Usage Information:_ We collect information about your use of the Services, including the type of browser you use, app version, access times, pages viewed, your IP address, and the page you visited before navigating to our Services. 
  * _Device Information:_ We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our Services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information. 
  * _Location Information_ In accordance with your device permissions, we may collect information about the precise location of your device. For more details, please see “Your Choices” below. 
  * _Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:_ We (and our service providers) use different technologies to collect information, including cookies, web beacons, and similar tracking technologies. A cookie is a small data file stored by your web browser on your computer or mobile device (hard drive) that helps us improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular, count visits, and prevent fraud. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. For more information about cookies and how to disable them, please see our Cookie Policy. 

When you purchase, return or exchange a product, we collect information about the transaction, such as product details, purchase price, and the date and location of the transaction. We also record customer service calls and capture video records and photographic information of you when you visit one of our stores. 

_Informaton We Collect from Other Sources_

We may also receive information about you from other sources and combine or link that with information we have about you. For example, we may collect information about you from third parties, including but not limited to change-of-address information or identify verification services if you apply for a job. 

## Use of Information

We use the information we collect to provide, maintain, and improve our Services and to offer you the finest products and shopping experience. We also use the information we collect to: 

  * Process your purchase transactions, fulfill your orders, and process exchanges and returns;
  * Send support and administrative messages, and respond to your comments, questions, and customer service requests; 
  * Communicate with you about products, services, offers, and events offered by Barneys New York and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you (if you prefer not to receive promotional communications from us, you may opt out at any time by following the instructions in the “Your Choices” section below); 
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with our Services and stores;
  * Detect, investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities and protect the rights and property of Barneys New York and others; 
  * Personalize your online experience and the advertisements and content you see when you use the Services based on your preferences, interests, and browsing and purchasing behavior; 
  * Facilitate contests, sweepstakes, and promotions and process and deliver entries and rewards; and
  * Carry out any other purpose described to you at the time the information is collected.

## Sharing of Information

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:

  * With vendors, consultants, and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf (for example, companies that help process, fulfill and ship orders, provide web hosting services, and distribute direct mail and marketing emails for us); 
  * With other companies for their own services and marketing purposes, unless you opt out of this type of sharing by writing to Barneys New York, Attn: Legal, 575 Fifth Avenue, New York NY 10017 or e-mailing privacy@barneys.com; 
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law or legal process, including lawful requests by public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements; 
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of Barneys New York or others; 
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company; 
  * Between and among Barneys New York and our current and future parents, affiliates, subsidiaries, and other companies under common control and ownership; or 
  * With your consent or at your direction.

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

## Social Sharing Features

The Services may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook “Like” button), which let you share actions you take on our social media pages. Your use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features. 

## Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others

We allow others to provide analytics services and serve advertisements on our behalf across the web and in mobile applications. These entities may use cookies, web beacons, device identifiers and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites and applications, including your IP address, web browser, mobile network information, pages viewed, time spent on pages or in apps, links clicked, and conversion information. This information may be used by Barneys New York and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other websites, and better understand your online activity. For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit www.aboutads.info/choices. 

Your device may also include a feature (“Limit Ad Tracking” on iOS or “Opt Out of Interest-Based Ads” or “Opt Out of Ads Personalization” on Android) that allows you to opt out of having certain information collected through apps used for behavioral advertising purposes. 

## Your Choices

_Online Account Information_

Registering for an account on our Services will make your online shopping experience faster and easier. We can store your shipping addresses and billing information so that you don’t have to enter them each time you shop. You will also be able to save your shopping basket, check your order status, and review your order history. In addition, you can seamlessly shop your favorite designers and products by saving them to your account. You can add, delete, or change your online account information at any time by logging into your account. If you wish to deactivate your account, please email us at privacy@barneys.com, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. 

_Location Information_

Barneys New York offers mobile applications that allow you to shop online, discover in-store happenings, browse editorial content, or receive other communications. When you first launch any of our mobile applications that collect location information, you will be asked to consent to the application’s collection of this information. Although you do not have to provide your location to use our mobile applications, allowing Barneys New York to collect precise location data enables us to deliver relevant content within our stores and to enhance your overall shopping experience. If you allow us to collect location information, we may collect your location at your request (such as when you tap “Enable” on a location services prompt). We may also collect location information when your device is near our in-store content personalization systems, even if you are not actively using the app. We use your location data to enhance your shopping experience, as well as to assist with foot traffic measurement and service improvements in our stores. If you initially consent to our collection of location information, you can subsequently turn off this location tracking at any time in your device settings, or by disabling Bluetooth. 

_Promotional Communications_

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Barneys New York by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations. 

_Mobile Push Notifications/Alerts_

With your consent, we may send promotional and non-promotional push notifications or alerts to your mobile device. You can deactivate these messages at any time by changing the notification settings on your mobile device. 

_Your California Policy Rights_

California law permits residents of California to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. Under the law, a business must either provide this information or permit California residents to opt in to, or opt out of, this type of sharing. Barneys New York qualifies for this alternative option. To opt out of having information about you shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes, you may do so by writing to Barneys New York, Attn: Legal, 575 Fifth Avenue, New York NY 10017 or e-mailing privacy@barneys.com. 

## Credit Card

If you have a Barneys New York credit card, a separate privacy policy describes collection, use, and protection of information about you and your account. To obtain a copy of our credit card privacy policy email privacy@barneys.com, or write Barneys New York, PO Box 326, Lyndhurst NJ 07071-0326. 

## Consumers in the European Economic Area

If you are in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), you have certain rights and protections under the law regarding the processing of your personal data. 

_Legal Basis for Processing_

When we process your personal data, we will only do so in the following situations:

  * We need to use your personal data to perform our responsibilities under our contract with you (e.g., processing payments for and providing the products or services you have requested). 
  * We have a legitimate interest in processing your personal data. For example, we may process your personal data to send you marketing communications, to communicate with you about changes to our Services, and to provide, secure, and improve our Services. 
  * We have your consent to do so. When processing is based on consent, you have the right to revoke such consent at any time by contacting us at privacy@barneys.com. 

_Data Retention_

We store the information we collect on you for as long as is necessary for the purpose(s) for which we originally collected it, or for other legitimate business purposes, including to meet our legal, regulatory, or other compliance obligations. 

_Transfer of Information to the U.S._

Barneys New York is based in the United States and we (and our service providers) process and store information in the U.S. If you reside outside the U.S., you understand and agree that we transfer your information to the U.S, which may not provide equivalent levels of data protection as your home jurisdiction. 

_Data Subject Requests_

You have the right to access personal data we hold about you and to ask that your personal data be corrected, erased, or transferred. You may also have the right to object to, or request that we restrict, certain processing. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, you can log into your account or may contact us at privacy@barneys.com. 

_Questions or Complaints_

If you have a concern about our processing of personal data that we are not able to resolve, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the data privacy authority where you reside. For contact details of your local Data Protection Authority, please see: http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: privacy@barneys.com

Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use information from and about you when you visit our website, create an account with us, visit our retail locations, or otherwise interact with us. This policy explains more about how we use cookies and your choices concerning cookies.   

## What are Cookies

Like most websites, we use cookies and similar technologies to remember things about you so that we can provide you with a better experience. 

  * Cookies are small data files stored on your browser or device. They may be served by the entity that operates the website you are visiting (“first-party cookies”) or by other companies (“third-party cookies”). For example, we partner with third-party analytics providers, like Google, which set cookies when you visit our websites. This helps us understand how you are using our Services so that we can improve them. 
  * Pixels are small images on a web page or in an email. Pixels collect information about your browser or device and can set cookies. 
  * Local storage allows data to be stored locally on your browser or device and includes HTML5 local storage and browser cache. 
  * SDKs are blocks of code provided by our partners that may be installed in our mobile applications. SDKs help us understand how you interact with our mobile applications and collect certain information about the device and network you use to access the application. 

## How We Use Cookies

We use cookies for a number of reasons, like helping us see which features are most popular, counting visitors to a page, improving our users’ experience, keeping our services secure, and generally providing you with a better experience. The cookies we use generally fall into one of the following categories. 

Category of Cookies | Why we use these cookies  
---|---  
Technical | These cookies are essential for our services to function properly. Like the other cookies we use, technical cookies may be either first-party cookies or third-party cookies.   
Preferences | We use these cookies to remember your settings and preferences. For example, we may use these cookies to remember your language preferences.   
Security | We use these cookies to help identify and prevent security risks.  
Performance | We use these cookies to collect information about how you interact with our services and to help us improve them.   
For example, we may use these cookies to determine if you have interacted with a certain page.   
Analytics | We use these cookies to help us understand improve our services.   
For example, we can use these cookies to learn more about which features are the most popular with our users and where we may need to make improvements.   
Advertising | Advertising We and our advertising partners use these cookies to deliver advertisements, to make them more relevant and meaningful to visitors to our website, and to track the efficiency of our advertising campaigns, both on our services and on other websites.   
  
Device IDs: If you access our website using a mobile device, the advertising identifier associated with your device or other identifiers may be recorded and used for purposes similar to those of cookies. We do not identify or record a device location without your specific permission. 

## Your Choices

You have a number of options to control or limit how we and our partners use cookies and similar technologies, including for advertising. 

  * Although most browsers and devices accept cookies by default, their settings usually allow you to clear or decline cookies. If you disable cookies, however, some of the features of our services may not function properly. 
  * To prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, you can install Google’s opt-out browser add-on.
  * For information on how our advertising partners allow you to opt out of receiving ads based on your web browsing history, please visit [http://optout.aboutads.info/](http://optout.aboutads.info/%22). European users may opt out of receiving targeted advertising through the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance.
  * You may see ads that are targeted to your interests on social media services. To learn more about the controls available to you on such social media sites, consult your settings on those services. 
  * Check your mobile device for settings that control ads based on your interactions with the applications on your device. For example, on your iOS device, enable the “Limit Ad Tracking” setting, and on your Android device, enable the “Opt out of Ads Personalization” setting. 

## Contact us

If you have any questions about our use of cookies, please contact us at Privacy@Barneys.com or at:

Barneys New York   
575 5th Ave   
New York, NY 10017   
Attn: Legal Department
